question_data = [
    {
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment: Music",
    "question": "Scatman John; real name was John Paul Larkin.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
    ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "The music video to The Buggle; Video Killed the Radio Star; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Korean girl group, TWICE, consists of 9 members",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "The song &quot;Stronger Than You; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "The 2011 movie;The Adventures of Tintin; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album Flood in 1990. ",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Stevie Wonder`s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "Muse is a British (English) rock band",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Music",
        "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]